what's up fam Dr Andy Galpin here and I
am stoked to be sharing something with
you that I've been working on in the
background for a very very long time you
see I can't count how many times over
the years I've been asked about
resources for science-based education
and information and knowledge in the
field of human performance and to be
honest with you I've never had a great
answer and I've never felt great about
that and so I teamed up with my man Dan
Garner and we built the thing ourselves
so ladies and Gent gentlemen welcome to
bom molecular
[Music]
athlete our vision here is simple and
clear build the best hub for
science-based Human Performance
education that the world has ever seen
see education is more than just
information to us here at biomolecular
athlete it's also the skills you need to
execute on the knowledge you've obtained
not only will this Hub be about
information courses research papers and
things like that it's also about the
Practical tools templates and other
tidbits you're going to want whether
you're an educator scientist athlete
coach trainer or anywhere in between but
our mission doesn't stop there as you
know Dan and I have made a career out of
democratizing science communication and
information and we are deeply passionate
and committed to continuing that so our
hope is that the small amount of things
behind the pay wall here at bom athlete
are enough to sponsor all the free stuff
we want to do have done are going to
continue to do and some of the things
we've got planned for the future I want
to acknowledge you Andy for the the
constant search of moving the human body
forward research that you're diving into
the constant testing the tweaking the
optimizing of humans because I've been
doing my blood work with Dan Garner but
I've been working with him like four
years now and dude it's like a secret
weapon I don't want people to know about
him at least not in my way class you
know me suan Ali was talking about this
Dan Garner they're working on a
concussion protocol to rehabilitate
people from concussions there're only a
handful meaning about three or four
people who I trust enough in the
exercise physiology space that when they
speak I not only listen but I modify my
protocols and you are among those three
or four people so whether you're
interested in achieving professional or
athletic Excellence or guiding others on
that Journey Bob molecular athlete
is the perfect spot for you so if any of
that resonated with you or you just are
interested in being on the front lines
and cutting edges of human performance
science and Physiology then come join us
here in the community at biomolecular
athlete and together let's see if we can
redefine and push the boundaries of
human
[Music]
performance